That could be the best one I've ever
tried. Oh my god.
>> Welcome back to my series where I
recreate Ben and Jerry's flavors, but
lower in calories and higher in protein.
This is everything but the. Let me show
you how to make it. So, obviously by my
dad's reaction, you guys know this one
is already a banger. Starting off with a
chocolate base. Everything But the has
chocolate and vanilla bases, but when
you mix the two, you basically get a
milk chocolate. So, that's the vibe I
was going for. Now, let's talk about the
mixins, which is the best part of
everything. But the You're going to need
chocolate covered toffee. I use Heath
Bar. Chocolate covered peanut butter
cups. I use Reese's. Chocolate covered
almonds. I use the ones from Trader
Joe's. And some white chocolate chips. I
use the sugar-free ones from Lily's. So,
chop all these up into your desired
size. And then, pro tip, freeze them.
This way, they don't get super broken up
when you run them on the mixing setting.
And that's it. Let's see what the
Everything But the Masters have to say.
But I'm the winner.
>> I'll be the judge of that base.
>> Can you say that again?
>> I said
that could be the best one I've ever
tried.
>> Oh my god, they just ate my whole pie.
We didn't type.